Feilin Han

\(+65 8941 1039

☑ adm-flhan@ntu.edu.sg

Singapore

Summary ___

My research interests mainly lie in Film PreViz and Virtual Production under virtual Environments, especially in Cinematic Virtual Reality (Virtual Cinematography, VR Previz, interactive VR filmmaking) and Digital Media Technology (Motion Capture, 3D Human Digitalization, Digital Asset Management), exploring immersion, interaction, and perception.

Education

Zhejiang University, Ph.D. in Digital Art and Design

Sept. 2014 to Dec. 2019

- Department of Digital Media Technology
- Research Interests: Motion Capture, Digital Human, 3D Animation.

Shandong University, B.S. in Digital Media Technology

Sept. 2010 to Jun. 2014

- School of Software Engineering
- **GPA:** 3.8/4.0.

University of California, Los Angeles, Summer School

July. 2011 to Sept. 2011

- · School of Theater, Film, and Television
- Courses: Introduction to Theater, Cinematography.

Experience _

Nanyang Technological University, Visiting Lecturer

Singapore

Nov. 2023 to Now

- The School of Art, Design and Media.
- **Teaching:** Virtual Reality and Stereo3D Production.
- FYP Supervisor: 3D Animation and Games in VR.

Beijing Film Academy, Lecturer

Beijing, China

Jan. 2020 to Nov. 2023

- Teaching: Virtual Reality Technology, Virtual Production.
- M.A./MFA Supervisor: Advanced Technology and Application in Film Production.

Bournemouth University, Visiting Scholar

Department of Film and TV Technology.

Bournemouth, UK Aug. 2016 to July 2017

- National Centre for Computer Animation.
- Marie Curie Research Fellow.
- Project: 3D Animation and Motion Capture.

Publications

An Analytical Study of Visual Attention Behavior in Viewing Panoramic Video

Nov. 2023

Feilin Han, Ying Zhong, Ke-Ao Zhao.

The 4th International Workshop on Human-centric Multimedia Analysis

A Metadata Generation System with Semantic Understanding for Video Retrieval in Film Production

Nov. 2022

Feilin Han, Zhaoxu Meng.

IEEE International Conference on Virtual Reality and Visualization (ICVRV)

Evaluating the Effect of Cinematography on the Viewing Experience in Immersive Environment

July 2022

Feilin Han, Ying Zhong, Minxi Zhou.

IEEE International Conference on Multimedia and Expo (ICME)

Projects _____

Austria Culture Heritage Digitization

Aug. 2023 to Now

- 360-degree panorama and Stereo3D video production.
- · Supported by European Capitals of Culture

Advanced Technology in Digital Film-making

Jan. 2021 to Dec. 2022

• Supported by National Social Science Fund of China.

Awards _____

Committee of 100 Scholars Program Award.

For Leadership, qualities, academic excellence, and community service Dec. 2018

Marie Curie International Incoming Fellowship

ERC 7th Framework Programme. July 2016

Skills ____

Languages: Native in Chinese (Mandarin), Professional in English, Intermediate in Korean

Software: Adobe Master Collection, Unreal Engine, Final Cut Pro, DaVinci Resolve